Guide to the University of Pittsburgh Archives Personal Files, 1824-present UA.Personal.Files
ULS Archives & Special Collections
University of Pittsburgh Archives Personal Files
1824-present
ULS Archives & Special Collections
UA.Personal.Files
64 Linear Feet
The University of Pittsburgh Archives Personal Files contain news clippings, press releases, photographs and other materials about University of Pittsburgh faculty, staff, administrators, students and visitors. There is at least one folder in the Information File for each of the headings listed below. The files are arranged in alphabetical order by last name and are available for public use in the Archives Service Center Reading Room. An asterisk after a name indicates that the file includes a photographic print or negative.
Acquisition Information
Created by the Archives Service Center staff since 1979.
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Health and medicine; Politics; Labor; Social action; Societies; Women; Architecture; Associations; Business and Industry; Churches and Synagogues; Education; Environment; Ethnic groups; Government
- A
  - Aaron, Deborah J.
  - Aaron, Seth
  - Abbe, George
  - Abbey, June C.
  - Abbot, Mark
  - Abdelhak, Merrat
  - Abdul, David
  - Abel, I. W. *
  - Abel, Raymond L.
  - Abell, Edward *
  - Abererombie, Elizabeth
  - Ablauf, Tom
  - Abo, Ben
  - Abraham, Andrew S.
  - Abraham, Donald (oversize) *
  - Abraham, Robert
  - Abramovitz, Max *
  - Abrams, Ellis
  - Abrams, Fred *
  - Abrams, Joel *
  - Abrams, Richard *
  - Abramson, Norman
  - Abromitus, Rebecca
  - Abu-Elmagd, Kareem
  - Acemoglu, Daron
  - Aceto, Mario D. G.
  - Acey, Alfred Edward
  - Ackenheil, A. C. (Mr. and Mrs.) *
  - Acker, Frank E. *
  - Ackerman, Diane
  - Ackerman, Eric
  - Acosta, Mayra M.
  - Adair-Hauck, Bonnie
  - Adams, Avery
  - Adams, Bernard *
  - Adams, Don K. (oversize)
  - Adams, Henry Richard
  - Adams, Jack
  - Adams, John William
  - Adams, Robert C.
  - Adams, Viers W. (oversize) *
  - Adderly, John (Rev. class of 1826)
  - Addis, Mattie B.
  - Adelman, Davis
  - Adelman, Fred
  - Adibi, Siamak (Dr.)
  - Adiele, Faith
  - Adjaye, Joseph
  - Adler, Sheldon, MD *
  - Adovasio, James M.
  - Affalder, L. J. *
  - Aftergood, Steven
  - Agarwala, Sanjiv
  - Agatisa, Patricia
  - Aghassy, Jacob *
  - Agnew, Daniel
  - Agnew, Robert (Dr.) *
  - Agostini, Michael
  - Agredono, Annette
  - Ahlarah, Solochidi
  - Ahearn, Joseph M.
  - Ahlbrandt, Roger, Jr. *
  - Ahlbrandt, Roger S., Sr. *
  - Ahner, Joachim
  - Ahren, Justen
  - Aizenman, Elias
  - Akbar, Na'im
  - Alarie, Yves
  - Alba, Danielle
  - Alba, Freddie
  - Albee, George W.
  - Albers, Kathryn M.
  - Albert, Mark
  - Albert, Walter
  - Alberter, Marilyn
  - Alberts, Robert
  - Alberts, Robert C. *
  - Albin, Maurice
  - Albrecht, Jill Marie
  - Albrecht, Susan Ann Kenney
  - Albrecht, Susan S.
  - Alden, Evan Dale
  - Alderman, Grover H.
  - Alderson, Daphne
  - Aldisert, Ruggero J. *
  - Alex, Jeff
  - Alexander, A. E.
  - Alexander, Elizabeth
  - Alexander, James R.
  - Alexander, Jane
  - Alexander, Livingston
  - Algeo, Donald
  - Algie, John
  - Ali, Robbie
  - Ali, Yusef
  - Alldred, Elizabeth *
  - Alldred, John *
  - Alldred, Joseph *
  - Alldred, Mary Jane *
  - Alldred, Peter *
  - Alldred, Sarah Collins *
  - Alldred, William Henry *
  - Allen, Alexander *
  - Allen, Catherine Louise *
  - Allen, Geri
  - Allen, Hervey *
  - Allen, Kathleen
  - Allen, Ralph Gilmore *
  - Allen, Sharon
  - Allen, Terrell
  - Alletto, Philip J.
  - Allinson, Gary D.
  - Allison, E. Jackson
  - Allison, James *
  - Allison, William H.
  - Allshouse, Cynthia
  - Allshouse, Richard
  - Al-Mirazi, Hafez
  - Almagno, Romano
  - Alman, Susan W. *
  - Alpern, Anne X.
  - Alpers, Melissa
  - Al-Sadet, Almira *
  - Alston, William (class of 1847)
  - Altamura, Robert
  - Altenburger, Christine *
  - Alter, Joseph
  - Altman, Isidore
  - Altshuller, Mark
  - Alvear, Cindy
  - Alxrander, Sir
  - Amano, Kozo
  - Amara, Susan G.
  - Ambuske, Gregory C.
  - Amdur, I.
  - Amelio, Gary A.
  - Amemiya, Shigeru
  - Amer, Ahmed
  - Ames, Barry
  - Amico, Janet
  - Amistade, Shawn
  - Amma, Elmer Louis
  - Amos, J. Ellwood (oversize) *
  - Amos, Thyrsa *
  - Amos, Wally
  - Amundson, Carroll J. *
  - Anderegg, F. O.
  - Anderson, Adolph G.
  - Anderson, Alan R. *
  - Anderson, Albert G.
  - Anderson, Bryan
  - Anderson, Carol
  - Anderson, Cheryl
  - Anderson, Elijah
  - Anderson, Elisabeth Mae
  - Anderson, George (oversize) *
  - Anderson, Jack
  - Anderson, John B.
  - Anderson, John H.
  - Anderson, Jon
  - Anderson, Joseph P.
  - Anderson, Kelly
  - Anderson, Louis
  - Anderson, Marty D.
  - Anderson, Melanie
  - Anderson, Nancy C.
  - Anderson, Paul D. *
  - Anderson, Ray
  - Anderson, Sada
  - Anderson, Stuart
  - Andes, Cynthia
  - Andic, Vojtech E.
  - Andrejasic, Henry
  - Andrews, George Reid
  - Andrews, Heather
  - Andria, George D.
  - Andrius, Otti
  - Angelou, Maya (Dr.)
  - Angulo-Galvis, Carlos
  - Angus, Derek C.
  - Anise, Emanuel
  - Annan, Kofi
  - Ansani, Nicole
  - Antaki, James
  - Antiqua, Orlando
  - Anthony, Edward *
  - Apadaca, Gerald
  - Apodaca, Gerard
  - Applebaum, Paul
  - Arabia, Anthony
  - Arac, Jonathan
  - Arbujas, Jorge
  - Arbuthnot, Thomas Shaw *
  - Archer, William Harry *
  - Archey, Mary Frances
  - Arensberg, Lili
  - Arey, David Gordon *
  - Arias, Rector *
  - Ariel, Michael
  - Arjmand, Ellis M.
  - Arlotta, Andrea
  - Armanios, Daniel
  - Armitage, John, MD *
  - Armour, Jody
  - Armstrong, Clyde A.
  - Arnaud, Sara *
  - Arndt, Karen
  - Arnett, Edward M. *
  - Arnold, Charles
  - Arnold, George
  - Arnold, Robert M.
  - Arnold, Russell *
  - Aronowsky, Michael
  - Aros, Sara H.
  - Arteaga, Jorge
  - Arthur, John M. *
  - Arthur, Robert *
  - Artman, J. Robert
  - Arueson, *
  - Aschkenas, David
  - Asdale, Will J.
  - Asenjo, Florencio Gonzalez
  - Ashbridge, Frank A.
  - Ashbrook, John J. *
  - Ashby, Aubrey L.
  - Ashcroft, John
  - Ashe, Bowman F.
  - Ashe, Lauren H. *
  - Asher, John William *
  - Asher, Sanford A.
  - Ashford, Douglas E.
  - Ashley, Kevin
  - Ashliman, D. L.
  - Ashman, Tia-Lynn
  - Asland, Reza
  - Asquith, Helen Jean Moore (SEE Moore, Helen Jean)
  - Astley, M. Royden
  - Astolfi, Douglas
  - Aston, Charles
  - Aston, Cheryl
  - Aston, Chris
  - Ataai, Mohommad
  - Atkins, Tom
  - Atkinson, Thomas *
  - Attardi, Barbara J. *
  - Attenberry, Phillip
  - Auble, Thomas
  - Aubyn, Frederick C. St.
  - Audette, Daniel
  - Aug, Mary Ann *
  - Auger, Becky
  - Aune, Bruce
  - Aung-Thwin, Maureen
  - Auslander, Tiger Paul *
  - Austern, Norman *
  - Austin, Sarah
  - Austin, Wanda
  - Aveni, Charles R. *
  - Averill, H. P.
  - Avery, Charles
  - Avery, Charlotte B.
  - Avery, Ellis
  - Avery, Harry
  - Avery, John C.
  - Avery, Robert W.
  - Avezzano, Joe
  - Avinoff, Andrey *
  - Axelrod, A. E. (Dr.)
  - Axelson, David
  - Ayars, Robert D. (oversize) *
  - Ayres, Erie B.
  - Ayub, Istiaque
- B
  - Babcock, Charlotte
  - Babcock, Edward V. and Mrs. *
  - Babones, Salvatore
  - Bacarisse, Pamela
  - Bacon, H. P.
  - Bacon, Raymond F.
  - Baderoon, Gabeda
  - Badie, Morsi
  - Badylak, Stephen
  - Baer, Townsend
  - Bagnato, Stephen J.
  - Bahar, Ivet
  - Bahnson, Henry T. *
  - Bahnson, Robert R. *
  - Baier, Annette C. *
  - Baier, Kurt *
  - Baierl, William
  - Bailey, Sadie F. *
  - Bailie, Robery
  - Bailie, Rolph (Dr.) *
  - Bair, G. J.
  - Baird, George M. P.
  - Baird, Thomas H. *
  - Bajwa, Neil
  - Baker, Carol
  - Baker, James A.
  - Baker, John
  - Baker, Clifford Bruce
  - Baker, Samuel E. W. (class of 1845)
  - Baker, Scott
  - Baker, Zelma *
  - Bakewell, Allan Campbell
  - Bakewell, Benjamin *
  - Bakewell, Thomas *
  - Balaski, Bob
  - Balazs, Anna C.
  - Baldrige, Edwin H.
  - Baldwin, Henry *
  - Baldwin, Leland Dewitt *
  - Baldwin, Robert
  - Baldwin, Wilmer E. *
  - Balich, Alecia
  - Balili, Ryan
  - Ball, Edward D.
  - Ball, Joe M. *
  - Ballantyne, Thrysa Amos *
  - Balliet, Kyle
  - Balliot, Robert
  - Balogna, John A., Jr. *
  - Balph, Eleanor H. *
  - Balph, Gail E.
  - Balph, Isabel M. *
  - Baltakas, Frank P.
  - Bambenek, Mark A.
  - Ban, Carolyn
  - Bandara, Geethanl
  - Bandik, George
  - Banerjee, Rajkumar
  - Banerjee, Sujata
  - Bangs, Ralph
  - Banks, Cora L.
  - Banks, Raymond A.
  - Banks, Richard L.
  - Banner, James E.
  - Barach, Joseph H. (Dr.)
  - Barand, Barbara W. *
  - Baranger, Elizabeth
  - Barankovich, George J.
  - Barber, James J.
  - Barber, Mary Ann
  - Barber, Theodore M.
  - Barbieri-Low, Anthony
  - Barco, Yolanda G.
  - Barenboim, Carl
  - Barker, Abner *
  - Barker, David C.
  - Barker, Robinson F. *
  - Barker, Thomas G. *
  - Barkley, Celeste
  - Barkley, Vernon M.
  - Barksdale, Edward M., Jr.
  - Barksdale-Hall, R. C.
  - Barlett, Janet A.
  - Barlow, Kevan
  - Barlow, Stanley
  - Barlow, Yolanda G.
  - Barmada, Michael
  - Barna, Roger L.
  - Barnard, John A.
  - Barnes, Corinne
  - Barnes, David
  - Barnes, Demas E.
  - Barnes, Edward *
  - Barnes, Roland E. *
  - Barney, W. David *
  - Barnhart, Barbara
  - Barnhart, Richard
  - Barnosky, Cathy
  - Barnwell, Ysaye M.
  - Baron, Richard L.
  - Barone, Charles J.
  - Barone, Eugene J.
  - Barr, Joseph M.
  - Barr, Matthew
  - Barranger, John
  - Barrett, Phil
  - Barrett, Tiffany
  - Barrick, William S., Jr.
  - Barrioneuvo, German
  - Barris, Gertrude W.
  - Barroll, John Leeds *
  - Barron, George
  - Barroso, Jose Manuel
  - Barrows, Leland
  - Barry, Herbert, III *
  - Barry, John R.
  - Barsom, Valentine *
  - Barsotti, Iacopa
  - Bart, Benjamin F.
  - Bartalotta, Vince *
  - Bartha, Denes Richard
  - Bartholomae, David
  - Bartlett, Janet A.
  - Bartley, William Warren
  - Barton, J. Clyde *
  - Barton, Spencer
  - Bartos, Otomar Jan
  - Barutha, Mitchel
  - Basford, Robert E.
  - Bashor, Nicole
  - Bass, Bernard M. *
  - Bass, Ellen
  - Bass, Lawrence W.
  - Bass, Tim
  - Batchelder, E. A.
  - Bates, Margaret W.
  - Bates, Theodore *
  - Batinski, Emily
  - Batista, Kenneth
  - Battaglia, Carmela
  - Battle, Stanley
  - Batz, Edna T. (Dr.) *
  - Bauer, Anthony
  - Bauhammers, Andrejs
  - Baum, Andrew
  - Baum, Bruce Jay
  - Baum, Martha
  - Baxter, Charles
  - Baxter, Graham *
  - Bayer, William J. *
  - Bayles, Constance M.
  - Bayles, Madeline
  - Bayles, Taryn
  - Baylis, Elena
  - Baynes, Darryl L.
  - Baynham, Edward G.
  - Bazin, Nancy Topping *
  - Beach, Scott
  - Beacock, Robert M.
  - Beal, George *
  - Beal, James (oversize)
  - Beall, Donald
  - Beaman, Jeanne *
  - Beamer, Ralph K.
  - Beams, Howard L.
  - Bean, Rita
  - Beard, Francis
  - Beard, Phillip
  - Beardslee, Clarissa Inda
  - Beardsley, Wallace R.
  - Bearer, Robert I.
  - Bearman, Toni Carbo
  - Beatrous, Frank H., Jr.
  - Beattie, Alfred W. *
  - Beatty, Jan
  - Beatty, Josephine R. (oversize) *
  - Beauchamp, Geoffrey L.
  - Beauregard, Robert A.
  - Bechtold, Judy
  - Beck, Carl *
  - Beck, Carolyn
  - Beck, Harry R.
  - Beck, Isabel
  - Beck, Joseph
  - Beck, Paul Allen
  - Becker, Dorothy J.
  - Beckman, Eric
  - Beckner, Marie E.
  - Beckwith, Sarah Thomasine
  - Beckwith, Thomas G. *
  - Bedford, Alfred Cotton
  - Bedford, Nathaniel
  - Beer, Thomas (class of 1826)
  - Beering, Steven C.
  - Beerman, Chris
  - Beerman, Lee
  - Beers, Armond H.
  - Beeson, Lillian L.
  - Begg, Lisa
  - Beeson, Lillian
  - Beeson, Patricia
  - Beidel, Deborah C.
  - Beikman, Donald
  - Beinecke, Brian
  - Beitel, Jason
  - Belani, Chandra P.
  - Belding, Harwood *
  - Belfour, C. Stanton (oversize)
  - Belkman, Eric
  - Belkner, Marie E.
  - Bell, Carl
  - Bell, Derrick A.
  - Bell, Frederick H.
  - Bell, Gwendolyn Dru'yor
  - Bell, Kenneth E.
  - Bell, Lloyd *
  - Bell, Louise N.
  - Bell, Michael
  - Bell, Robert
  - Bell, Walter Dwight (class of 1832)
  - Bell, William M. (class of 1830)
  - Bell-Loncella, Elizabeth T.
  - Bellack, Alan S.
  - Belle, Steven
  - Belmonte, Jeff
  - Belnap, Nuel
  - Belowich, David
  - Belzer, Jack
  - Bemis, Leo *
  - Bender, Catherine
  - Bender, Gregor
  - Bender, John R., Jr.
  - Bender, Martin S. *
  - Bender, Reagan
  - Bender, Roger S.
  - Bendet, Irwin
  - Bendig, Albert William
  - Beneder, Theresa *
  - Benedicty, Mario *
  - Benedum, Michael L.
  - Benjamin, Lloyd *
  - Benjamin, Roger
  - Benn, C. L.
  - Benner, Raymond C.
  - Bennet, Michael
  - Bennewitz, Margaret
  - Benson, D. M. et al
  - Benson, Neal T.
  - Benson, Robert
  - Bent, Henry A.
  - Benter, William F.
  - Bentley, Marian
  - Bently, Ronald
  - Benton, Catherine
  - Bentz, Michael
  - Benveniste, Mathilde
  - Benz, Ed
  - Beranek, William (Dr.) *
  - Beratan, David
  - Beratan, Kathy
  - Berenato, Agnus
  - Berg, Charles A.
  - Berga, Sarah
  - Berge, Eleanor H.
  - Berger, Allen
  - Berger, Arnold Herman
  - Berger, George S.
  - Berger, J. Alfred *
  - Berger, Vincent F. *
  - Bergman, H. David
  - Bergman, Jeff
  - Berkebile, Carole
  - Berkebile, Paul E.
  - Berkely, Elizabeth
  - Berkey, Bernice M.
  - Berkey, Edgar
  - Berkowitz, Daniel
  - Berkowitz, Morris
  - Berkshire, Logan
  - Berkun, Alvin K.
  - Berman, David M.
  - Bermann, Marc
  - Bern, Joseph
  - Bernardo, Lisa
  - Bernhardt, Homer
  - Bernier, George *
  - Berns, Gregory S.
  - Beroes, Charles *
  - Berrian, Brenda
  - Berring, Thilde *
  - Berry, David
  - Berry, Harry *
  - Bertocci, Gina
  - Bertolini, Fernando *
  - Berztiss, Portrzit *
  - Bessey, Otto A.
  - Bessolo, Gina
  - Besterfield-Sacre, Mary
  - Bethe, Monica
  - Betheuin, John
  - Beuthin, John
  - Beverly, John
  - Bevier, George M. *
  - Bey, Ernest
  - Bhargava, Bharat
  - Bhaskaran, Sita
  - Bhatnagar, Rakesh K.
  - Bhopti, Shahrooz
  - Bi, Gud-Qiang
  - Biagini, Mary Kay *
  - Bianculli, J. A. *
  - Bicanich, Thomas P. *
  - Bickel, William E. *
  - Bidanda, Bopaya
  - Biddle, J. F.
  - Biddle, Theodore W. (oversize) *
  - Bidwell, Charles *
  - Biegart, Edward C.
  - Biehler, Allen D.
  - Bierman, Morris I. *
  - Bigelow, Sheila
  - Biggs, Charles F. *
  - Biggs, Shirley *
  - Bigley, Thomas G. *
  - Bigos, Joseph
  - Bigos, Kristin
  - Bikerman, Michael
  - Bilivakis, Michael
  - Billiar, Timothy R.
  - Billick, Dean
  - Billman, Carol
  - Biloen, Paul
  - Bimes, unknown *
  - Biondi, Angelo Mario *
  - Biondi, Manfred
  - Birch, Jack W. *
  - Bircher, Jane
  - Bircher, Nicholas
  - Birdwhistell, Ray L.
  - Birkett, Daryl
  - Birkle, Jenna
  - Birmaher, Boris
  - Birnbaum, David
  - Birnberg, Jacob *
  - Bisco, Ralph
  - Bishop, Frederic Lendall *
  - Bishop, Maryann
  - Bishop, Sandra L.
  - Biskup, Janet
  - Bissinger, H. G.
  - Bittinger, Mark
  - Bittner, Lorraine
  - Bittner, William
  - Bjerke, Richard J.
  - Bjorhovde, Reider
  - Blachere, Jean
  - Black, Andrew Watson
  - Black, Dwight L.
  - Black, Edwin
  - Black, G. S. (Dr.)
  - Black, Harold B.
  - Black, John (Rev.) *
  - Black, John (class of 1825)
  - Black, Robert John (class of 1840)
  - Black, Robert M. (oversize) *
  - Black, Samuel W.
  - Blackburn, James B.
  - Blackburn, Raymond F. *
  - Blackett, Richard
  - Blackington, Frank H.
  - Blackmond, Donna G.
  - Blackmore, David
  - Blackwood, O. H.
  - Blair, Allen G.
  - Blair, Andrew *
  - Blair, Deborah
  - Blair, Jacob *
  - Blair, Peter
  - Blaisdell, George G.
  - Blake, David *
  - Blake, Deborah
  - Blakely, Edward *
  - Blakesles, Elmer F.
  - Blanchere, Jean
  - Blanck, Peter
  - Blank, Stephen *
  - Blanton, John
  - Blanton, Latonya
  - Blanton, Thomas S.
  - Blasi, Elizabeth Marie
  - Blasier, Cole *
  - Blatnica, Amber
  - Blatt, Genevieve
  - Bleaney, B. (Dr.)
  - Bledsoe, Anthony
  - Blee, Kathleen M.
  - Blevins, Anna
  - Blevins, Richard
  - Bliss, William H. *
  - Block, Alvan M.
  - Block, Geoffrey D.
  - Block, Henry W.
  - Block, Karen
  - Blodgett, Todd
  - Blolard, Sue Erikson
  - Blomster, R.
  - Bloom, Marc
  - Bloomer, William *
  - Bluestone, Charles D. *
  - Blum, Eva
  - Blum, Sandy
  - Blumberg, David
  - Blumberg, John
  - Blumenschein, Frederick J.
  - Blumenthal, Monica D.
  - Boas, George *
  - Boateng, E. A. *
  - Bob, Clifford
  - Bobenage, Judith
  - Bober, Phyllis Pray
  - Bobick, James
  - Bobrow, Davis B.
  - Bochenski, Joseph M.
  - Bock, Shelly
  - Bodenschatz, Carl D.
  - Bodnar, Lisa M.
  - Boehm, Marc
  - Boerio, Bibiana
  - Boer, Arend E. *
  - Bogen, James
  - Boggs, Dane R.
  - Boggs, Joseph C. *
  - Boggs, Roy
  - Boggs, Sallie S.
  - Bogue, R. H.
  - Bogusch, George *
  - Boldurian, Anthony T.
  - Boles, Traci Lee
  - Bolette, David Paul
  - Bollendorf, Bill
  - Boltacz, Paul R. *
  - Bolvin, John
  - Bom, David
  - Bomhard, Emma
  - Bomhard, Miriam L. (oversize)
  - Bompiani, Enrico
  - Bonach, Mary *
  - Bonar, Jeffrey
  - Bonasorte, Charles
  - Bonci, Leslie
  - Bond, Lloyd
  - Boneva, Bonka
  - Bonham, Andy
  - Boni, Arthur A.
  - Boninger, Michael
  - Bonk, Janet
  - Bonn, Robert
  - Bonnenberg, Heinrich
  - Bonner, Kenyon
  - Bony, John
  - Booker, Sherideu
  - Bookstaver, David Richard
  - Boone, Troy
  - Boota, Ahmad
  - Boote, Robert
  - Booth, August Marshall, Jr.
  - Booth, William W. Trustee *
  - Boothe, Willis Anson
  - Boots, Ralph Simpson
  - Bopp, Barbara
  - Bordern, R. S. *
  - Bordne, Erich *
  - Borghetti, E. J.
  - Borguet, Eric
  - Borkowski, Casimir
  - Borle, Andre B.
  - Borovetz, Harvey S.
  - Borton, Georgina
  - Borza, Nikki
  - Bosnyak, Zsolt
  - Bossen, Laurel
  - Boston, Robert
  - Bothner-By, Aksel (Dr.)
  - Botkin, Jeffrey
  - Botset, H. G. (Prof.) *
  - Bott, Margaret M.
  - Boucher, Richard A.
  - Boundreau, Joseph
  - Boures, Emil
  - Bourgeois, Louis
  - Bourret, Tim
  - Boutros, Osiris
  - Bouvier, Peter L.
  - Bove, Paul A.
  - Bowen, Al
  - Bowen, Donald D.
  - Bowers, James L. *
  - Bowers, John *
  - Bowers, Keely
  - Bowman, Barbara
  - Bowman, John G. (oversize) *
  - Bowman, John R. (son of John G.)
  - Bowman, Ned *
  - Bowman, Sherri L.
  - Bowman, Theodore *
  - Bowness, J. M. (Dr.)
  - Bowser, Charley
  - Bowser, Elsworth T.
  - Bowser, Robert
  - Bowser, Ruth Farrell
  - Boyce, Doreen
  - Boyd, Amber
  - Boyd, Courtney
  - Boyd, Linda Wharton
  - Boyd, Rick
  - Boyer, Herbert W.
  - Boyer, William W. *
  - Boyle, JoAnne
  - Boyle, Richard
  - Bozik, Edward (oversize)
  - Bozso, Franz
  - Brach, Jennifer S.
  - Brach, Paul
  - Bracken, John
  - Brackenridge, Caroline Marie *
  - Brackenridge, Henry M. *
  - Brackenridge, Hugh Henry *
  - Brackman, Richard T.
  - Braden, Ina
  - Braden, Marcia H.
  - Bradford, Donald C.
  - Bradley, Doris P.
  - Bradley, Ernestine
  - Bradley, James P.
  - Bradley, Nezlan
  - Brady, John D., Sr.
  - Brailey, Lestier G.
  - Brainard, Alan J. *
  - Brake, Deborah
  - Brambley, Angie
  - Bramhall, David *
  - Branson, Douglas
  - Bramson, Paul
  - Bran, Rita
  - Branch, Robert Anthony
  - Brand, Dionne
  - Brand, Roland A.
  - Brand, Ronald
  - Brand, Thurlow W. *
  - Brand, Uwe
  - Brandt, Max
  - Brandes, Oliver L.
  - Brandom, Barbara
  - Brandon, Robert
  - Branigan, Ruth
  - Branning, Rosalind L.
  - Branson, Douglas M.
  - Brant, Robert
  - Brashear, John A.
  - Braude, Abraham
  - Braughler, Mark I.
  - Braumhammers, Andrejs
  - Braun, Arthur *
  - Braun, Harry *
  - Braun, Laura M. *
  - Braun, Thomas
  - Braziel, Cindy
  - Brechbill, Nancy
  - Breeze, Jean "Binta"
  - Bregenser, Henry G.
  - Brehm, F. J. L. *
  - Breight, Curt
  - Breitfeld, Volker
  - Breneman, Richard H.
  - Brennan, William
  - Brenner, Michael
  - Brennet, Namoli
  - Brent, David
  - Breuning, Stephen E.
  - Brewer, D. J. *
  - Brice, Albert
  - Brice, Cindy
  - Brice, Heather
  - Brice, William R.
  - Brickley, Kathleen Gallant
  - Brickner, Anthony
  - Brictson, Robert C.
  - Bright, Mike
  - Brill, Carli
  - Brinckloe, William Draper *
  - Brinda, John, Jr. (oversize) *
  - Briner, Jamie
  - Brinker, William E., Jr. *
  - Brinkman, Baba
  - Brinton, Charles
  - Brinton, William M., MD *
  - Briscoe, Mary Louise
  - Britell, Robert *
  - Brittain, Raymond F. *
  - Britton, Cynthia
  - Britvec, Stanko J. *
  - Broaded, C. Montgomery
  - Broadhurst, James S.
  - Broadhurst, Suzanne W.
  - Brack, Timothy C. *
  - Brockenbrough, Princell
  - Brockington, Deneene
  - Brodbeck, David
  - Broderick, Dorothy M. *
  - Broderick, John
  - Broder, David
  - Brodhead, David *
  - Brodsky, Jeffrey
  - Brody, H. D.
  - Brody, Michael C. *
  - Bromberg, Philip
  - Bromeley, Robert
  - Bromfield, Ben
  - Bromley, Robert
  - Bron, Klaus M.
  - Brookhart, J. D.
  - Brooks, Benjamin T.
  - Brooks, Clyde
  - Brooks, Glidden L.
  - Brooks, Stanley T.
  - Brooks, Thomas
  - Bronsin, Henry W.
  - Brosius, Arthur J. *
  - Brosius, Eva Reid
  - Broughton, Philip S.
  - Broussard, Elsie R.
  - Brouwer, Joel
  - Brown, Bishop (oversize) *
  - Brown, Carol Museley
  - Brown, Cheryl
  - Brown, David Lee
  - Brown, David T.
  - Brown, Donald B.
  - Brown, Doris
  - Brown, Douglas
  - Brown, Harrison M.
  - Brown, Homer (Judge) *
  - Brown, Jaron
  - Brown, Jason
  - Brown, Johnnie
  - Brown, Kristin
  - Brown, L. A. *
  - Brown, L. Keith
  - Brown, Louise
  - Brown, Mitchell
  - Brown, Rachel
  - Brown, Robert C. *
  - Brown, Robert K.
  - Brown, Ron
  - Brown, Scarlett
  - Brown, Selena
  - Brown, Sherry Miller
  - Brown, Stuart I.
  - Brown, Tony
  - Brown, William J.
  - Browne, Anna Moody *
  - Browne, Robert Audley *
  - Brownell, Celia
  - Browning, Diana C.
  - Browning, Douglas M.
  - Broz, Geoff
  - Brubaker, Brian
  - Brubaker, Clifford E.
  - Brubaker, Dianne B.
  - Bruce, David H. *
  - Bruce, George D. *
  - Bruce, Jennifer
  - Bruce, Kirk
  - Bruce, R.
  - Bruce, Robert *
  - Brufsky, Adam
  - Bruder, Mary
  - Bruhns, Fred C.
  - Bruhns, Maxine E.
  - Brumble, David
  - Brummond, Kay M.
  - Brundu, Benedetta
  - Brunger, Thomas *
  - Bruns, Frank
  - Brunot, Felix R. *
  - Brush, Billy
  - Brush, Lisa
  - Brusilovsky, Peter
  - Brustein, William I.
  - Brutus, Dennis
  - Bryan, Fred
  - Bryan, Teddy
  - Bryant, Antonio
  - Bryant, Bill
  - Bryant, John L., II
  - Bryson, Allan M.
  - Bryson, Michael
  - Brzoza, Tom
  - Buchanan, Bruce G.
  - Buchanan, John Jenkins
  - Buchanan, Sally
  - Bucheit, Karen Niemic
  - Buchele, Tom
  - Bucher, Alison
  - Buchsbaum, Ralph *
  - Buchter, Elizabeth Ann
  - Buck, Lewis N. (oversize) *
  - Buckley, Joseph
  - Buckner, Chester A.
  - Buckstein, Oscar
  - Buckwalter, Kimberly J.
  - Buckwalter, T. V. *
  - Busco, John
  - Buechler, Joseph *
  - Bueing, Thilde *
  - Bujak, Malgorzata
  - Bulick, Stephen
  - Buliga, Marius
  - Bulik, Cindy (Dr.)
  - Bullen, Graham (Dr.) *
  - Bullman, Sandy
  - Brumble, H. David
  - Bunch, Ted *
  - Bunker, Clareann
  - Bunting, Clair
  - Burckhaltor, T. W.
  - Burd, Martin
  - Burdett, Ray
  - Burdis, Loni
  - Burge, Barbara J.
  - Burgert, Jody
  - Burgess, David R.
  - Burgi, Ernest
  - Burgio, Louis
  - Burgos, Ariel
  - Burke, Charles J.
  - Burke, Charles "Chip", III
  - Burke, Donald
  - Burke, Glema C.
  - Burke, Lora
  - Burke, Marilyn
  - Burke, Patrick J. *
  - Burke, Ruth Ann
  - Burket, Clifford A.
  - Burkholder, Rick
  - Burkhart, Eugene L.
  - Burkoff, John M.
  - Burks, C. J.
  - Burnim, Kalman A.
  - Burns, Helen
  - Burns, Keiven *
  - Burnstine, Deidre
  - Burr, Keith (oversize)
  - Burroughs, Joan
  - Burstin, Barbara
  - Burt, Robert C.
  - Burzachechi, Nancilee
  - Bush, David R.
  - Bush, Esther
  - Bushnell, Candace
  - Buss, Arnold H. *
  - Butler, James
  - Butler, Paul
  - Butler, Peter R.
  - Butler, Ruth
  - Butler, Shirley Ann
  - Butters, Meryl
  - Buzzell, Anne *
  - Byerly, Richard Taylor
  - Byers, Lorena (SEE Garloch, Lorena A.)
  - Byers, Lyle W.
  - Byers, Virginia
  - Byham, William C. *
  - Byrd, James
  - Byrne, George Dennis
  - Byrne, Robert F. *
  - Bytheway, Joan
  - Bytheway, Rob
- C
  - Cacali, Mary
  - Cade, Arthur R.
  - Caenap, Rudolf
  - Caffey, John P.
  - Caggiula, Anthony
  - Caggiula, Arlene
  - Caginalp, Gunduz
  - Cahalane, Helen
  - Cahen, Michael
  - Cahouet, Frank V.
  - Cain, James